RBRL/082/GGA
Richard B. Russell Library for Political Research and Studies
- VII. Photographs, 1985-2003; 21.0 boxes; (23 linear feet)
  - A. Member Photographs, 1999, undated; 1229 photographs, 466 negatives, and 1 electronic file
    - Barbara Bunn, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 38)
    - Roger Byrd, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 39)
    - Gene Callaway, [Portraits, 1 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 40)
    - Tom Campbell, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 41)
    - Henrietta Canty, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 42)
    - Hanson Carter, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 43)
    - Matt Caseman, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 44)
    - Steve Cash, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 45)
    - Don Castleberry, [Portraits, 1 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 46)
    - R. M. Channell, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 47)
    - Mike Cheokas, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 48)
    - Buddy Childers, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 49)
    - Mike Coan, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 50)
    - Bill Clark, [Portraits, 2 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 51)
    - Jim Cole, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 52)
    - Brooks Coleman, [Portraits, 6 (3.5x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 53)
    - Terry Coleman, [Portraits, 6 (5x7) color; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 54)
    - Jack Connell, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 7 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 55)
    - Sharon Cooper, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 56)
    - Clay Cox, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 57)
    - Kathy Cox, [Portraits, 3 (3.5x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 58)
    - Mack Crawford, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (3.5x5) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 59)
    - Ronnie Culbreth, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 60)
    - Bill Cummings, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 61)
    - Grace Davis, [Portraits, 1 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 62)
    - Max Davis, [Portraits, 5 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 63)
    - Steve Davis, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 64)
    - Tommy Davis, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 65)
    - Jay Burke, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 66)
    - Douglas Dean, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 67)
    - Buddy Deloach, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 68)
    - George Deloach, [Portraits, 5 (4x5 5x7); 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 69)
    - Tom Dickson, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 70)
    - Scott Dix, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 71)
    - Harry Dixon, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 72)
    - Denny Dobbs, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 73)
    - Ron Dodson, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 74)
    - Pat Dooley, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative] (Box VII.1, Folder 75)
    - John Douglas, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 76)
    - Winfred Dukes, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 77)
    - Beth Durden, [2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 78)
    - Earl Ehrhart, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 79)
    - Chris Elrod, [Portriats, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 80)
    - Terry England, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 81)
    - Carl Epps, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 82)
    - Mike Evans, [Portaits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 83)
    - Doug Everett, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 84)
    - Dorothy Felton, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 85)
    - Johnny Floyd, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 8 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 86)
    - Virgil Fludd, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 87)
    - Ron Forster, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 89)
    - Bobby Franklin, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 90)
    - Allen Freeman, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 91)
    - Harry Geisinger, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 92)
    - Rich Gouk, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 93)
    - David Graves, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 6 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 94)
    - Gerald Greene, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; pictures, 3 (4x6) color; 3 (4x6) b/w; 5 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 95)
    - George Grindley, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 96)
    - Bob Hanner, [Portraits, 5 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 97)
    - Ben Harbin, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 98)
    - Sally Harrell, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 99)
    - John Heard, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 100)
    - Keith Heard, [1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 101)
    - Joe Heckstall, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 102)
    - June Hegstrom, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 103)
    - Bill Hembree, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 104)
    - Michele Henson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 105)
    - Roger Hines, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 1 (4x5) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 106)
    - Robert Hobbs, [Portraits, 7 (4x5) color; 10 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 107)
    - Ray Holland, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 5 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 108)
    - Bob Holmes, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 109)
    - Doug Holt, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 110)
    - Billy Horne, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 111)
    - Penny Houston, [Portraits, 6 (4x5) color; 6 (5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 112)
    - Henry Howard, [Portraits, 1 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 113)
    - Ralph Hudgens, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 114)
    - Newt Hudson, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 115)
    - Sistie Hudson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 116)
    - Carolyn Hugley, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 117)
    - Bob Irvin, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 118)
    - Bill Jackson, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 119)
    - Lester Jackson, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 5 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 120)
    - Lynmore James, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 121)
    - Janette Jamison, [Portraits, 1 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 122)
    - Charles Jenkins, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 123)
    - Curtis Jenkins, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 124)
    - Paul Jenings, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 125)
    - Shelia Jones, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 126)
    - Darryl Jordan, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 8 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 127)
    - Brian Joyce, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 128)
    - Mitchell Kaye, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 129)
    - Mike Keown, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 130)
    - David Knight, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 131)
    - Charles Ladd, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 132)
    - Dan Lakly, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 133)
    - Bob Lane, [Portraits, 7 (4x5 5x7); 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 134)
    - Roger Lane, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 135)
    - Bill Lee, [Portraits, 1 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 136)
    - Jeff Lewis, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 137)
    - Edward Lindsey, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 138)
    - Jimmy Lord, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 139)
    - Billy Loudermilk, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 140)
    - David Lucas, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 141)
    - Jon Lunsford, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 142)
    - George Maddox, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 134)
    - Randall Mangham, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 135)
    - Harold Mann, [Portraits, 1 (4x5) color; 1 (5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 136)
    - Judy Manning, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 4 (3.5x5 5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 137)
    - Jim L. Martin, [Portraits, 4 (2.5x3.5 5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 138)
    - Jeff May, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 139)
    - Chuck Martin, [4 Negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 141)
    - Pete Martin, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7); 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 140)
    - Jim Martin, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 142)
    - Warren Massey, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 143)
    - Louise McBee, [Portraits, 5 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 144)
    - Tim McCall, [Portraits, 4 (4x5 5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 145)
    - Joann McClinton, [1 negative.] (Box VII.1, Folder 146)
    - Billy McKinney, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 8 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 147)
    - Fran Millar, [Portraits, 6 (4x5) color; 6 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.1, Folder 148)
    - Alicia Morgan, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.1, Folder 149)
    - Nick Moriatakis, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 1)
    - Greg Morris, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 2)
    - Howard Mosby, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 3)
    - Hinson Mosley, [Portraits, 5 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 4)
    - Ann Meuller, [Portraits, 4 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 5)
    - Robert Mumford, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 6)
    - Mike Muntean, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 7)
    - Jack Murphy, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 8)
    - Quincy Murphy, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 9)
    - Tom Murphy, [Portraits, 8 (5x7) b/w; pictures, 1 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives; 1 slide.] (Box VII.2, Folder 10)
    - Jay Neal, [Portraits. 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 11)
    - John Noel, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 12)
    - James Mills, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 13)
    - Barbara Mobley, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 14)
    - Bert Oliver, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 15)
    - Earl O’Neal, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 16)
    - Nan Orrock, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 17)
    - Bobby Parham, [Portraits, 9 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 18)
    - Butch Parrish, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; pictures, 3 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 19)
    - Don Parsons, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 20)
    - Dorothy B. Pelote, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 21)
    - Tim Perry, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 22)
    - Judy Poag, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 23)
    - Dan Ponder, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 24)
    - Dubose Porter, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 25)
    - Alan T. Powell, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 26)
    - Alan R. Purcell, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 27)
    - Arnold Ragas, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 28)
    - Billy Randall, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 29)
    - Robert Ray, [Portraits, 4 (4x5 5x7) b/w; 3 (4x5) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 30)
    - Henry Reaves, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 5 (various sizes) b/w; 8 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 31)
    - Barbara Reece, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 32)
    - Stacey Reece, [Portraits, 7 (4x5 5x7) color; 4 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 33)
    - Kasim Reed, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 34)
    - Bobby Reese, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 35)
    - Bobby Reese, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 36)
    - Robert Reichert, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 37)
    - Tom Rice, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 38)
    - Glen Richardson, [Portraits, 6 (5x7 8x10) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 39)
    - Lawrence Roberts, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative] (Box VII.2, Folder 40)
    - Carl Rogers, [Portraits, 5 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 41)
    - Richard Royal, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 42)
    - Ron Sailor, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 43)
    - Bill Sanders, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 44)
    - Randy Sauder, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 45)
    - Stephen Scarlett, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 46)
    - Austin Scott, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 47)
    - Martin Scott, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 48)
    - Valencia Seay, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 49)
    - Ed Setzler, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 50)
    - Tom Shanahan, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 51)
    - Jay Shaw, [Portraits, 4 (4x5) color; 7 (4x5 5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 52)
    - Charles Sheid III, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 53)
    - Tom Sherrill, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 54)
    - Kemuel Shipp, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 55)
    - Wallace Sholar, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 4 (2.5x3 5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 56)
    - Chuck Sims, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 57)
    - Georgana Sinkfield, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; pictures, 2 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 58)
    - Jimmy Skipper, [Portraitrs, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 59)
    - Bob Smith, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 60)
    - Charles Smith, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 61)
    - Clint Smith, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 7 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 62)
    - Larry Smith, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 63)
    - Lynn Smith, [Portraits, 5 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 64)
    - Paul Smith, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 3 (5x7) color; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 65)
    - Tommy Smith, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 5 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 66)
    - Vance Smith, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 67)
    - Calvin Smyre, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 68)
    - Bob Snelling, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 69)
    - Mike Snow, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 4 (4x5 5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 70)
    - Mary Squires, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 71)
    - Tracy Stallings, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 72)
    - Frank Stancil, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 73)
    - Steve Stancil, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 6 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 74)
    - Lannett Stanley, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 75)
    - Pamela Stanley, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 76)
    - Ron Stephens, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 77)
    - Dough Stoner, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 78)
    - Willie Talton, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 79)
    - Maretta M. Taylor, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 80)
    - Sharon Teague, [Portraits, 1 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 81)
    - Rob Teilhet, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 83)
    - Doug Teper, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 84)
    - Brian Thomas, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 85)
    - Regina Thomas, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 86)
    - Theo Titus, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 87)
    - Scott Tolbert, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 88)
    - Curt Thompson, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 89)
    - E. C. Tillman, [Portrits, 3 (4x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 90)
    - Allen Hammon Tree, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 91)
    - Sharon Trense, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 92)
    - Steve Tumlin, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 93)
    - Henrietta E. Turnquest, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 94)
    - Ralph Twiggs, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 95)
    - Renee Unterman, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 96)
    - Larry Walker, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 2 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 97)
    - Len Walker, [Portraits, 2 (5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 98)
    - Pete Warren, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 99)
    - Stan Watson, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 100)
    - Jack West, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 3 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 101)
    - Wendall Willard, [Portraits, 4 (4x5) b/w; 10 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 102)
    - Lynn Westmoreland, [Portraits, 6 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 4 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 103)
    - Ben Whitaker, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 104)
    - John Wiles, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 105)
    - Joe Wilkinson, [Portraits, 6 (4x5 5x7) color; 1 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 106)
    - Al Williams, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 107)
    - Coach Williams, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) color.] (Box VII.2, Folder 108)
    - Jeff Williams, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 2 negatives.] (Box VII.2, Folder 109)
    - Robin Williams, [Portraits, 3 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 110)
    - Betty Jo Williams, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 111)
    - Don Wix, [Portraits, 2 (4x5) color; 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 112)
    - John Yates, [Portraits, 3 (5x7) b/w; 1 negative.] (Box VII.2, Folder 113)
    - Portraits of Sonny Perdue [User copy], undated (Item EM-362-367)
  - B. Daily Photographs, 1983-2005; 2470 photographs, 4951 sets of negatives, and 61 35mm film strips
    This sub-series is arranged chronologically and consists primarily of negatives depicting the daily activities in the House and group images.
    - [407 sets of negatives, box 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box VII.B.1)
    - [117 sets of negatives, box 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box VII.B.2)
    - [448 sets of negatives, box 1 of 2], 1987 (Box VII.B.3)
    - [117 sets of negatives, box 2 of 2], 1987 (Box VII.B.4)
    - [374 sets of negatives, box 1 of 2], 1988 (Box VII.B.5)
    - [112 sets of negatives, box 2 of 2], 1988 (Box VII.B.6)
    - [444 sets of negatives], 1989 (Box VII.B.7)
    - [463 sets of negatives], 1990 (Box VII.B.8)
    - [427 sets of negatives, box 1 of 2], 1991 (Box VII.B.9)
    - [66 sets of only negatives, 9 sets of only photos, 19 sets of photos and negatives, 319 individual photos total, box 2 of 2], 1991 (Box VII.B.10)
    - [22 sets of only negatives, 8 sets of only photos, 5 sets of photos and negatives, 787 individual photos total, box 1 of 2], 1992 (Box VII.B.11)
    - [31 sets of only negatives, 7 sets of only photos, 1272 individual photos total, box 2 of 2], 1992 (Box VII.B.12)
    - [317 sets of negatives], 1992-1993 (Box VII.B.13)
    - [280 sets of negatives, 2 individual photos, 45 displaced 35mm film strips, 1 booklet of descriptions for (7/10/95-8/18/95)], 1994-1995 (Box VII.B.14)
    - [103 sets of negatives, 29 individual photos, 6 displaced 35mm film strips], 1996 (Box VII.B.15)
    - [276 sets of negatives], 1997-1998 (Box VII.B.16)
    - [425 sets of negatives, 10 individual photos], 1999-2000 (Box VII.B.17)
    - [360 sets of negatives, 3 individual photos, 10 displaced 35mm film strips], 2001-2002 (Box VII.B.18)
    - [138 sets of negatives], 2003 (Box VII.B.19)